{
  "HOME.CHANGE_LANG": "العربية",
  "HOME.HERO.BIG_TEXT": "Your Pets' Needs,\nArrive Automatically.",
  "HOME.HERO.TEXT": "With Petlo Autoship you can schedule your pets' needs and get them regularly, so you  will never run out of pet food or other essentials like litter and treats again.",
  "HOME.DOWNLOAD.IOS_FIRST_TEXT": "Download on the",
  "HOME.DOWNLOAD.IOS_SECOND_TEXT": "App Store",
  "HOME.DOWNLOAD.ANDROID_FIRST_TEXT": "Get it on",
  "HOME.DOWNLOAD.ANDROID_SECOND_TEXT": "Google Play",
  "HOME.TESTIMONIALS.TITLE": "What Petloers Said about Us",
  "HOME.TESTIMONIALS.TEXT": "Download The App and Be The Next Petloer!",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.TITLE": "How to Create an Autoship?",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.1": "After downloading & opening the app, go to the 'Autoship' tab, and click 'Create an Autoship'.",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.2": "Fill in the Autoship information. name, items, delivery address, payment method, for whom this Autoship from your pets to make it unique and to get some surprises for the included pets 😉, and then add when the Autoship should arrive.",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.3": "On the page 'When should it arrive?', you need to set when the first shipment should arrive. Then you need to set when should it recur.",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.4": "Before creation, you can check all the Autoship information like when should it arrive and the amount. When you're done you can click the 'Create' button.",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.5": "Now on the Autoship page, you will see all the Autoships that you have, or you can create new ones.",
  "HOME.HOW_IT_WORKS.6": "When clicking on the 3 dots icon on any Autoship you have, you can always change anything from there, skip the next shipment, or deactivate the Autoship.",
  "HOME.MORE_THINGS.TITLE": "Other Features in Petlo",
  "HOME.MORE_THINGS.TITLE_1": "The Shop",
  "HOME.MORE_THINGS.DESCRIPTION_1": "Want something in an hour or the next day, without scheduling? You can visit 'Petlo Shop' page and you can order traditionally.",
  "HOME.MORE_THINGS.TITLE_2": "Personalize Your Journey",
  "HOME.MORE_THINGS.DESCRIPTION_2": "Add your pets to your account, so you can customize Orders or Autoships, to get some surprises for the included pets 😉.",
  "HOME.COMMON_QUESTIONS": [
    {
      "title": "G COMMON_QUESTIONS",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "How do I create an Autoship so that I can receive recurring shipments?",
          "answer": "1. Click on the 'Create an Autoship' button.{{br}}2. Add the name of the Autoship so that you can distinguish it, choose the products that you want to schedule, then choose your preferred payment method, and then you have to choose the date of the first shipment and when it should recur after that, and you can also add the names of the pets for which this Autoship is created if you wish.{{br}}3. After filling out the information, you can create your first Autoship, and wait for your shipments to arrive."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Autoship COMMON_QUESTIONS",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "What is Autoship?",
          "answer": "Autoship enables you to schedule your pets’ needs and ship them on a regular basis, so you will never run out of pet food or other essentials like litter and treats again."
        },
        {
          "question": "How do I create an Autoship so that I can receive recurring shipments?",
          "answer": "1. Click on the 'Create an Autoship' button.{{br}}2. Add the name of the Autoship so that you can distinguish it, choose the products that you want to schedule, then choose your preferred payment method, and then you have to choose the date of the first shipment and when it should recur after that, and you can also add the names of the pets for which this Autoship is created if you wish.{{br}}3. After filling out the information, you can create your first Autoship, and wait for your shipments to arrive."
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the benefits of Autoship?",
          "answer": "Any Autoship you create will give you a 5% discount on the total amount of all the items you added to the Autoship.{{br}}Note: The discount includes the total items cost, and does not include the delivery cost."
        },
        {
          "question": "Are there any fees?",
          "answer": "No, scheduling your pets’ needs is completely free, and you can stop the Autoship whenever you want."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I cancel the Autoship?",
          "answer": "Yes, absolutely. When you already have an Autoship, you will see all the Autoships that you previously created. Click on the three dots icon, then choose 'Deactivate Autoship' and then press the confirmation button to complete the process of canceling the Autoship.{{br}}Note: You can reactivate the Autoship at any time you want, just by clicking on the 'Reactivate' button and then choosing the date of the next shipment and when it should recur."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I change the scheduling date?",
          "answer": "Yes, absolutely. When you already have an Autoship, you will see all the Autoships that you have previously created. Click on the three dots icon, then choose 'Change Shipments Dates' and then you can change the scheduling information and the date of the next shipment."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I skip the Autoship shipment?",
          "answer": "Of course, you can, When you already have an Autoship, you will see all the Autoships that you have previously created. Click on the three dots icon, then choose 'Skip Next Shipment' and then press the confirmation button to skip the shipment.{{br}}For example, if your next shipment is on the 8th and the recurrence period is every 10 days, the shipment on the 8th will be skipped and become on the 18th."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I change the Autoship items?",
          "answer": "Of course, when you already have Autoship, you will see all the Autoships that you previously created. Click on the three dots icon, then choose 'Change Items', after which you can remove or add any item you want, and the new price for the added items will appear before confirming the change."
        },
        {
          "question": "How can I pay?",
          "answer": "You can pay with Cash on Delivery, or by using a Card."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I change my payment method?",
          "answer": "Yes, you can always change the payment method to (Cash on Delivery, or Card) or you can change or add a new Card to use.{{br}}When you already have Autoship, you will see all the Autoships that you previously created. Click on the three dots icon, then choose 'Change Payment Method' and then you can change and save the changes."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I change the shipping address?",
          "answer": "Yes, of course, you can change your shipping address or add a new address to ship shipments to it.{{br}}When you already have an Autoship, you will see all the Autoships that you previously created. Click on the three dots icon, then choose 'Change Shipping Address' and then you can change and save the changes."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I cancel the Autoship shipment before it arrives?",
          "answer": "Of course, if you no longer need the order on the day specified for the shipment to arrive, don’t worry. A Petlo representative will contact you and you can inform him of this before delivery."
        },
        {
          "question": "When will my shipment arrive?",
          "answer": "On the same day that was specified, a Petlo representative will contact you to confirm and choose the appropriate hour for delivery."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I track the shipping status?",
          "answer": "You can always see the autoship information and the date of the next shipment from the 'Autoships' page.{{br}}You can track the status of the shipment on the day specified for shipment from the 'Orders' page."
        },
        {
          "question": "How many Autoships can I create?",
          "answer": "You can create an unlimited number of Autoships, you can also add all your pet’s items in one Autoship, or you can customize each Autoship for a pet, it's up to you."
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_1_TITLE": "5% Discount on Items Cost",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_1_DESCRIPTION": "With Petlo Autoship get a 5% discount on your scheduled items cost.",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_2_TITLE": "Ability to Change Items",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_2_DESCRIPTION": "Whatever the reason, you can add new items to your Autoship, or even remove items that you no longer need.",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_3_TITLE": "Skip the Next Shipment or Reschedule the Delivery Date",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_3_DESCRIPTION": "Easley if you no longer need the next shipment at the time you picked beforehand, you can skip it or change the delivery time to something suitable.",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_4_TITLE": "Cancel the Autoship with 3 Clicks",
  "AUTOSHIP_FEATURES_4_DESCRIPTION": "Whatever the reason, you can cancel your Autoship at any moment with just 3 clicks.",
  "SUPPORT.TITLE": "Support",
  "SUPPORT.DESCRIPTION": "We whould be pleased to support you. Send us a message on WhatsApp at our phone number +962790174799, or Email us at support@petlo.co.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_1": "Privacy",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_1": "Al Khalili LTD built the Petlo app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Al Khalili LTD at no cost and is intended for use as is. This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service. If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which are accessible at Petlo unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_2": "Information Collection and Use",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_2": "For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to name, phone number, location, and card number. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. The app does use third-party services that may collect information used to identify you.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_3": "Log Data",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_3": "We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third-party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_4": "Cookies",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_4": "Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device's internal memory. This Service does not use these cookies explicitly. However, the app may use third-party code and libraries that use cookies to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_5": "Service Providers",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_5": "We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons: \n\n * To facilitate our Service \n\n * To provide the Service on our behalf \n\n * To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. \n\n We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to their Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_6": "Security",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_6": "We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_7": "Changes to This Privacy Policy",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_7": "We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. This policy is effective as of 20-09-2023",
  "PRIVACY.TITLE_8": "Contact Us",
  "PRIVACY.DESCRIPTION_8": "If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at support@petlo.co."
}
